{
    "unit1": [{
            "question": "7 + (-13)",
            "answer": "-6"
        },
        {
            "question": "-9 + (-3)",
            "answer": "-12"
        },
        {
            "question": "100 + 5",
            "answer": "105"
        },
        {
            "question": "35 - (-5)",
            "answer": "40"
        },
        {
            "question": "9 - 50",
            "answer": "-41"
        },
        {
            "question": "26 - 9 + (-17)",
            "answer": "0"
        },
        {
            "question": "-46 + 46",
            "answer": "0"
        },
        {
            "question": "100 + (-500)",
            "answer": "-400"
        },
        {
            "question": "-9 - (-5) + 6",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "14 - 42 - 9",
            "answer": "-37"
        },
        {
            "question": "-6 + 2 - (-16)",
            "answer": "12"
        },
        {
            "question": "50 - 23 + (-7)",
            "answer": "20"
        }

    ],
    "unit3": [{
            "question": "1/2",
            "answer": "0.5"
        },
        {
            "question": "3/11",
            "answer": "0.27..."
        },
        {
            "question": "- 3/2",
            "answer": "-1.5"
        },
        {
            "question": " 6/9",
            "answer": "0.6..."
        },
        {
            "question": " 1/3",
            "answer": "0.3..."
        },
        {
            "question": "5/20",
            "answer": "0.25"
        },
        {
            "question": "7/8",
            "answer": "0.875"
        },
        {
            "question": " 11/33",
            "answer": "0.3..."
        },
        {
            "question": " 2 1/3",
            "answer": "2.3..."
        },
        {
            "question": "4/25",
            "answer": "0.16"
        },
        {
            "question": "8/25",
            "answer": "0.32"
        },
        {
            "question": "14/33",
            "answer": "0.42..."
        }

    ],
    "unit2": [{
            "question": "6 x (-5)",
            "answer": "-30"
        },
        {
            "question": "-14 x (-6)",
            "answer": "86"
        },
        {
            "question": "-172 / 2",
            "answer": "-86"
        },
        {
            "question": "-2(-6) + 5(-3)",
            "answer": "-3"
        },
        {
            "question": "100 / (-50)",
            "answer": "-2"
        },
        {
            "question": "-7 x (-4) + 5)",
            "answer": "-23"
        },
        {
            "question": "(-5) x (-5) - 5",
            "answer": "20"
        },
        {
            "question": "(5) x (-5) - 5",
            "answer": "-30"
        },
        {
            "question": "(-5) x (-5) x (0)",
            "answer": "0"
        },
        {
            "question": "3(-5) x (-5) + 5",
            "answer": "80"
        },
        {
            "question": "8(6) / (17 - 5)",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "(-2) x (-2) x (-2) x (-2)",
            "answer": "16"
        }

    ]

}